<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CSC415-UIBasics</string>
    <string name="button_label_toast">Toast</string>
    <string name="button_label_count">Count</string>
    <string name="toast_message">Hello Toast!</string>
    <string name="count_initial_value">0</string>
    <string name="button_label_zero">Zero</string>
    <string name="article_text"><b> Automata theory </b> is the study of abstract machines and automata, as well as the computational problems that can be solved using them. It is a theory in theoretical computer science. The word automata (the plural of automaton) comes from the Greek word αὐτόματος, which means "self-acting, self-willed, self-moving". An automaton (Automata in plural) is an abstract self-propelled computing device which follows a predetermined sequence of operations automatically. An automaton with a finite number of states is called a Finite Automaton (FA) or Finite-State Machine (FSM).
\n\n
The figure at right illustrates a finite-state machine, which belongs to a well-known type of automaton. This automaton consists of states (represented in the figure by circles) and transitions (represented by arrows). As the automaton sees a symbol of input, it makes a transition (or jump) to another state, according to its transition function, which takes the previous state and current input symbol as its arguments.
\n\n
Automata theory is closely related to formal language theory. In this context, automata are used as finite representations of formal languages that may be infinite. Automata are often classified by the class of formal languages they can recognize, as in the Chomsky hierarchy, which describes a nesting relationship between major classes of automata. Automata play a major role in theory of computation, compiler construction, artificial intelligence, parsing and formal verification. </string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><i>From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia www.wikipedia.com</i></string>
    <string name="article_title">Automata theory</string>
</resources>